<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HateID</string>
    <string name="Neighbourhood_Dispute_Result">If, in your judgement, the client has not been victimised by hate, but by a neighbourhood dispute, please see Northumbria Police guidance to give appropriate advice <a href = "https://www.northumbria.police.uk/advice/advice-and-information/asb/asb/antisocial-behaviour/disputes-with-neighbours"><font colour = "@colour/purple">Here</font></a>.</string>
    <string name="Anti_Social_Behaviour_Result">If, in your judgement, the client has not been victimised by hate, but by anti-social behaviour, please refer them to your ASB Team. See: [hyperlink to Northumbria Police ASB page].</string>
    <string name="Crime_Result">1. If, in your judgement, the client is in danger/at risk and or the victim of a crime encourage them to CONTACT THE POLICE</string>
    <string name="Crime_Hate_Result">If, in your judgement, the client is in danger/at risk and or the victim of a crime that is motivated by hate then encourage them to CONTACT THE POLICE and REPORT A HATE CRIME.</string>
    <string name="Non_Crime_Incident_Result">If, in your judgement, the client is in danger/at risk and or the victim of a non-crime incident that is motivated by hate then encourage them to CONTACT THE POLICE and REPORT A HATE INCIDENT.\n\nIf, in your judgment, the client is the victim of a non-crime incident then please refer them to CONNECTED VOICE HATE CRIME ADVOCACY SERVICE (HCAS).</string>
    <string name="Mate_Crime_Hate_Result">If, in your judgement, the client is in danger/at risk and or the victim of a mate crime that is motivated by hate then encourage them to CONTACT THE POLICE and REPORT A HATE CRIME.\n\n\n\nIf, the client has been victimised by mate crime, please refer them to ADULT SERVICES: \n\nNorthumberland \n\nNorth Tyneside \n\nSouth Tyneside \n\nNewcastle \n\nGateshead \n\nSunderland\n\n\nIf, in your judgment, the client is also/or in need of emotional and/or practical support for mate crime they have experienced, please refer to the CONNECTED VOICE HATE CRIME ADVOCACY SERVICE (HCAS).</string>
    <string name="Mate_Non_Crime_Hate_Result">If, in your judgement, the client is in danger/at risk and or the victim of a mate-related non-crime incident that is motivated by hate then encourage them to CONTACT THE POLICE and REPORT A HATE INCIDENT.\n\nIf, the client has been victimised by a mate-related non-crime incident, please refer them to ADULT SERVICES: \n\nNorthumberland \n\nNorth Tyneside \n\nSouth Tyneside \n\nNewcastle \n\nGateshead \n\nSunderland\n\nIf, in your judgment, the client is also/or in need of emotional and/or practical support for a mate-related non-crime incident they have experienced, please refer to the CONNECTED VOICE HATE CRIME ADVOCACY SERVICE (HCAS).</string>
    <string name="Hate_Relationship_Crime_Result">If, in your judgement, the client is in danger/at risk and or the victim of a hate relationship then encourage them to CONTACT THE POLICE and REPORT A HATE CRIME.\n\nIf, in your judgment, the client is the victim of a hate relationship [including a crime] then please refer them to CONNECTED VOICE HATE CRIME ADVOCACY SERVICE (HCAS).</string>
    <string name="Hate_Relationship_Non_crime_Result">If, in your judgment, the client is the victim of a hate relationship [including only non-crime incidents] then please refer them to CONNECTED VOICE HATE CRIME ADVOCACY SERVICE (HCAS).</string>
    <string name="Hate_Crime_And_Hate_Relationship_Result">If, in your judgement, the client is in danger/at risk and or the victim of a crime that is motivated by hate as well as a victim of a hate relationship then encourage them to CONTACT THE POLICE and REPORT A HATE CRIME.\n\nIf, in your judgment, the client is the victim of a hate relationship [including a crime] then please refer them to CONNECTED VOICE HATE CRIME ADVOCACY SERVICE (HCAS).</string>
</resources>